<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<string id="igi_task_text_done">
		<text>Job done. Time to return to task giver.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- mutant -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_mutant_title">
		<text>Eliminate dangerous mutants</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mutant_descr">
		<text>My job is to eliminate mutants in this area.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mutant_job_descr">
		<text>Recently some mutants have appeared and are threatening our operations. The commander is seeking someone who can take care of them. Here, take a look.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mutant_finish">
		<text>Great job! They didn't let our teams work...</text>
	</string>
	<!-- supply -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_supply_title">
		<text>Supply chain</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_supply_descr">
		<text>My task is to neutralize the guards and deliver the containers.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_supply_job_descr">
		<text>Our patrols has reported the location of the supply unit at these coordinates. For some reason, the caravan has not yet reached the location of the group. They may have been hindered by mutant activity, bad weather, emissions, or something else. Search their caravan. Their supplies will be useful to our group. We will not stand for gratitude.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_supply_finish">
		<text>Honest pay for honest work. These things are really good, indeed.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- heavy -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_heavy_title">
		<text>Neutralization</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_heavy_descr">
		<text>I need to neutralize a group of enemy stalkers at this location.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_heavy_job_descr">
		<text>Recently, a group of enemies appeared not far from us. It seems that these guys are quite capable for you, but do not overdo it - they are well-staffed and clearly looking for trouble. Good hunting, Stalker.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_heavy_finish">
		<text>No problems, I hope? These guys were clearly ready for a fight. Excellent work.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- transaction -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_transaction_title">
		<text>Transaction</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_transaction_descr">
		<text>These bastards have betrayed their groups. My job is to kill them all. They will have a deal at the designated location.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_transaction_job_descr">
		<text>A friend of mine decided to start a rat hunt in his group. I won't go into details - your task is to come to the meeting place and pick up the goods. By force. Bring the product to me, and I'll find a use for it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_transaction_finish">
		<text>Good job. They owe me a drink for this one. Here is your share.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- artifact_world -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_artifact_world_title">
		<text>Artifacts for everyone, for free</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_artifact_world_descr">
		<text>Doctor said that an artifact could be found here. Let's try my luck, then.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_artifact_world_job_descr">
		<text>Our guys spotted the artifact as they were passing by. They had injured people with them, so they passed this information on to me. Since you have proven yourself well, I will give you this information for free. Keep working for our faction and you'll get a lot more.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_artifact_world_finish">
		<text>Nothing. This line will not be shown in the game.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- artifact_stalker -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_artifact_stalker_title">
		<text>Artifact "Hunting"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_artifact_stalker_descr">
		<text>Doctor told me this guy had an artifact. He isn't very friendly though...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_artifact_stalker_job_descr">
		<text>This guy's group was looking for artifacts when our guys passed by. Don't you want to help the guy with his heavy load, so to speak?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_artifact_stalker_finish">
		<text>Nothing. This line will not be shown in the game.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- weapon -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_weapon_title">
		<text>Equip</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_weapon_descr">
		<text>I have the opportunity to upgrade my equipment. I should use it..</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_weapon_job_descr">
		<text>It seems that our enemy has a promising squad, and their equipment is quite good. Don't you want to test your strength and weaken our enemies? And their gear will be your reward.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_weapon_finish">
		<text>Nothing. This line will not be shown in the game.</text>
	</string>
</string_table>