<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<!-- This file contains text for tasks from base anomaly -->
<!-- If task has exclusive text, then it's here -->
<!-- Pattern for text: *task_id*_*whatever part* -->
<string_table>
	<!-- Barkeep -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_bar_visitors_barman_stalker_trader_task_assault_monster_online_title">
		<text>Destroy the Mutants</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_bar_visitors_barman_stalker_trader_task_assault_monster_online_descr">
		<text>Barkeep has hired me to clear out a lair of mutants.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_bar_visitors_barman_stalker_trader_task_assault_monster_online_job_descr">
		<text>Some of my boys got torn up real bad by mutants on the way back from their last expedition. Duty promised to purge the lair in retaliation, but they just haven't gotten around to it. Will you take this on for me?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_bar_visitors_barman_stalker_trader_task_assault_monster_online_finish">
		<text>Sweet vengeance. Good work, here's the money.</text>
	</string>
		<string id="igi_task_bar_visitors_barman_stalker_trader_task_kill_stalker_title">
		<text>Kill the Stalker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_bar_visitors_barman_stalker_trader_task_kill_stalker_descr">
		<text>I've agreed to take care of a stalker for the Barkeep.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_bar_visitors_barman_stalker_trader_task_kill_stalker_job_descr">
		<text>One of the regulars around here turned out to be rotten to the core. Rostok would more than happily pay to put flowers on his grave, if you catch my drift. So, are you up for it?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_bar_visitors_barman_stalker_trader_task_kill_stalker_finish">
		<text>Here is your money, just don't get carried away with murdering too much.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- OLIVIUS -->
		<string id="igi_task_val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_assault_stalkers_title">
	    <text>Turf War</text>
		</string>
	<string id="igi_task_val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_assault_stalkers_descr">
		<text>I've agreed to stick up a stalker camp for Olivius. He mentioned that I might need to bring friends.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_assault_stalkers_job_descr">
		<text>This one is a real cinch. Sultan's got a mind to shake down a nearby stalker camp; shake things up, remind them who's in charge around here. You'll need to get your own little gang together for this, but there's big props in it for you if you can pull it off.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_assault_stalkers_finish">
		<text>Ha! Well done! I hope you stripped off all the loot you could; here's a little extra from me.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="igi_task_val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_kill_stalker_title">
		<text>Hit Man</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_kill_stalker_descr">
		<text>Olivius has contracted me to run a hit on some poor sucker, then return for payment.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_kill_stalker_job_descr">
		<text>I've got a list of people who've rubbed me the wrong way. I want you to rub one of them out. What do you say?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_kill_stalker_finish">
	    <text>Good, you got rid of that asshole! Here is what I promised.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="igi_task_text_val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_assault_monster_online_title">
		<text>Eliminate Mutant Threat in Dark Valley</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_assault_monster_online_descr">
		<text>Mutants have been spotted near this location making the area dangerous. You have been tasked to eliminate the mutant threat within the area. Report back to Olivius after the job is done.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_assault_monster_online_job_descr">
		<text>We've been looking for someone with enough balls to clear out mutants in a few places. Stalkers aren't coming around here because they are too afraid. If we don't do something about it we won't have anyone left to 'borrow' any goods from, then we will have to move out of this territory.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_assault_monster_online_finish">
		<text>Fantastic! Here is your payment. I'll make sure to put a good word in for you with the boss.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- WOLF -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_assault_monster_online_title">
		<text>Eliminate the Mutant Threat from Cordon</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_assault_monster_online_descr">
		<text>I've agreed to clear out a mutant lair for Wolf, which will no doubt make life much easier for stalkers in Cordon. I'll need to return to him for payment once the job is complete.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_assault_monster_online_job_descr">
		<text>Though this is the border of the Zone, newbies have it tough even here. The bandits are only half the problem - they at least understand Russian. But the mutants - it's really tough with them. If you're an able hunter, there's a mutant lair not far from here that needs to be cleared out. If you manage to do this, I'll owe you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_assault_monster_online_finish">
		<text>Thank you, stalker. Maybe the rookies around here will take this chance to learn a thing or two before becoming pig food. Ah, right. I said I'd owe you. Here's your payment.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- FANATIC -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_assault_monster_online_title">
		<text>Destroy the Mutant Lair</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_assault_monster_online_descr">
		<text>I've agreed with Fanatic to destroy a mutant lair for the sake of the stalkers in Cordon.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_assault_monster_online_job_descr">
		<text>Yeah, there's a small issue that needs sorting out. Cordon is supposed to be one of the safest places in the Zone, yet a new mutant lair has sprung up not too far from here. It needs to be cleared before it gets too large - otherwise, the rookies here will be in for a grave time. So, what do you say? Will you do it?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_assault_monster_online_finish">
		<text>Great work. Thanks to you, the rookies will have more room to breathe without being thrown into the deep end. Here's your payment - they all contributed a little to it. </text>
	</string>
	<!-- BUTCHER -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_hunter_gar_trader_task_assault_monster_online_title">
		<text>Cull Hunting</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_hunter_gar_trader_task_assault_monster_online_descr">
		<text>Butcher isn't happy with the frequency of mutant activity around here. I've agreed to thin the herd in return for a reward.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_hunter_gar_trader_task_assault_monster_online_job_descr">
		<text>Some of the mutant species around here are getting too large in numbers for my liking. It's necessary to keep their populations from getting too high, or animal aggression levels could spike, overwhelming local stalkers. If you are capable enough to do this for me, I'll compensate you for your skill. Don't forget to bring back any meat or trophies you find, to sell for a bonus! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_hunter_gar_trader_task_assault_monster_online_finish">
		<text>Once again the local ecosystem is in balance, and hunting can remain a useful pastime, rather than a dire necessity. Here's your reward for a job well done.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- TRAPPER -->
	<string id="igi_task_jup_b220_trapper_task_kill_stalker_title">
		<text>Assassinate target</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_jup_b220_trapper_task_kill_stalker_descr">
		<text>Trapper has a high value target that needs to be eliminated.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_jup_b220_trapper_task_kill_stalker_job_descr">
		<text>I have a dangerous threat that needs to be eliminated. Not a mutant this time, but a man. He will not be easy to get to but I promise to pay you well. Are you up for the job?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_jup_b220_trapper_task_kill_stalker_finish">
		<text>Excellent work stalker. Here is your payment.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="igi_task_text_jup_b220_trapper_task_assault_monster_online_title">
		<text>Clear area of mutants</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_jup_b220_trapper_task_assault_monster_online_descr">
		<text>Mutants have been spotted near this location making the area dangerous for some of the locals. You have been tasked to lead a hunting party to reduce the mutant threat within the area. Report back to Trapper after the job is done.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_jup_b220_trapper_task_assault_monster_online_job_descr">
		<text>I have organized a hunt to help keep the area around Yanov a bit safer by depopulating the various mutant lairs found in area. I need someone experienced to lead it. Would you like the job?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_jup_b220_trapper_task_assault_monster_online_finish">
		<text>Thank you, stalker. The area will be much safer for others because of you. Here is your payment.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- BEARD -->
	<string id="igi_task_zat_a2_stalker_barmen_task_kill_military_stalker_title">
	<text>My Brother's Keeper</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_zat_a2_stalker_barmen_task_kill_military_stalker_descr">
		<text>Kill the Military Stalker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_zat_a2_stalker_barmen_task_kill_military_stalker_job_descr">
		<text>There's a guy; used to be a regular stalker just like anyone else on this ship. One day, some Military officers came and offered him a commission. The next thing we knew, he's found murdering his former brothers in cold blood! We cannot stand for that! Find this traitor and avenge the men he shot in the back.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_zat_a2_stalker_barmen_task_kill_military_stalker_finish">
		<text>Ah, you killed him? Help yourself to a drink. I'm sure we could all do with one...</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_a2_stalker_barmen_task_assault_monster_online_title">
		<text>Clear area of mutants</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_a2_stalker_barmen_task_assault_monster_online_descr">
		<text>Mutants are about. Hunt them down and clear the area.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_a2_stalker_barmen_task_assault_monster_online_job_descr">
		<text>Shh... Listen, hear that? Some mutants howling. Still gives me the chills after all this time. How about you go out there and take care of them? I'll make it worth your while.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_a2_stalker_barmen_task_assault_monster_online_finish">
		<text>Haha! Well done, stalker! Have a drink on Beard!</text>
	</string>
	<!-- Kuznetsov -->
<string id="igi_task_text_agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_assault_stalker_title">
		<text>Under the Rug</text>
	</string>
<string id="igi_task_text_agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_assault_stalker_descr">
		<text>Colonel Kuznetsov has asked me to terminate a group of stalkers at the marked location.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_assault_stalker_job_descr">
			<text>There's one delicate matter. The presence of illegals near our base is not advantageous for our future operations. The assignment is this: any authorized personnel or Duty forces you find at the marked location are allowed to go free, but otherwise all those present must be terminated, no matter what agreements they think they have with us. Do you understand? </text>
	</string>
		<string id="igi_task_text_agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_assault_stalker_finish">
		<text>Great job. Keep it up, and you'll be in line for a commendation.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="igi_task__task_kill_stalker_title">
		<text>Martial Justice</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task__task_kill_stalker_descr">
		<text>The Zone is a popular haven for all manner of scum and villainy. Colonel Kuznetsov has singled out a target for me to execute.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task__task_kill_stalker_job_descr">
		<text>The SSU keeps me furnished with a list of its most-wanted targets. Some of them are known spies or enemy tacticians. Others - I'm ashamed to say - are deserters, dishonourable insects who have abandoned their comrades-in-arms.  And others still are little better than common scum - criminals from the outside world who fled into the Zone to escape justice. The exact crime committed doesn't matter. What matters is one such target has made himself vulnerable. If you are willing to be his executioner, you can expect a bonus in your next paycheck. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task__task_kill_stalker_finish">
		<text>Outstanding work! The ministers at Internal Affairs will be pleased.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- Petrenko -->
	<string id="igi_task_bar_dolg_general_petrenko_stalker_task_assault_stalkers_title">
		<text>Defend Rostok</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_bar_dolg_general_petrenko_stalker_task_assault_stalkers_descr">
		<text>Colonel Petrenko has asked me to eliminate a group of stalkers that have been posing a threat to Duty.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_bar_dolg_general_petrenko_stalker_task_assault_stalkers_job_descr">
		<text>The situation is becoming unfavourable. Enemies gather all over the Zone. I'm sending my men out to a few of our adversary's rally points before our foes can properly muster an attack, can you handle this one?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_bar_dolg_general_petrenko_stalker_task_assault_stalkers_finish">
		<text>Excellent work. Your service does you credit.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="igi_task_bar_dolg_general_petrenko_stalker_task_kill_stalker_title">
		<text>Neutralize Target for Petrenko</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_bar_dolg_general_petrenko_stalker_task_kill_stalker_descr">
		<text>Colonel Petrenko has ordered me to find and eliminate a target.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_bar_dolg_general_petrenko_stalker_task_kill_stalker_job_descr">
		<text>I have some subjects that need removal. The targets are usually murderers, rapists, defectors, enemy operatives or strategists. This target is currently our most urgent. Take him out, and you'll help not only Duty but all right-minded people who work in the Zone.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_bar_dolg_general_petrenko_stalker_task_kill_stalker_finish">
		<text>Great! You do us proud, and such diligence shall not go unrewarded.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- Barkeep -->
	<string id="igi_task_bar_visitors_barman_stalker_trader_task_kill_stalker_title">
		<text>Kill the Stalker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_bar_visitors_barman_stalker_trader_task_kill_stalker_descr">
		<text>I've agreed to take care of a stalker for the Barkeep.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_bar_visitors_barman_stalker_trader_task_kill_stalker_job_descr">
		<text>One of the regulars around here turned out to be rotten to the core. Rostok would more than happily pay to put flowers on his grave, if you catch my drift. So, are you up for it?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_bar_visitors_barman_stalker_trader_task_kill_stalker_finish">
		<text>Here is your money, just don't get carried away with murdering too much.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- Sultan -->
	<string id="igi_task_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_kill_stalker_title">
		<text>Mob Hit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_kill_stalker_descr">
		<text>Sultan has sent me to eliminate some bum, then return for my payment.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_kill_stalker_job_descr">
		<text>See this list? This is a list of rats I need exterminated.\n \n...Cheapskates who chose to cut and run rather than pay their debts.\n \n...Misers who answered with bullets when my boys begged them for bread.\n \n...Bitches and traitors that left Dark Valley to kowtow to Rostok or Sidorovich.\n \nThey can all go fuck themselves. Here; a name off my list. I'd like you to let me know when I can cross it out.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_kill_stalker_finish">
		<text>Ah, cold satisfaction. I like it when shit goes down smoothly. Here, a token of my gratitude.</text>
	</string><string id="NE RABOTAETigi_task_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_kill_stalker_title">
		<text>Stalker Elimination</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="NE RABOTAETigi_task_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_kill_stalker_descr">
		<text>Sultan has sent me to enact vengeance on some stalkers that harassed one of his boys.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="NE RABOTAETigi_task_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_kill_stalker_job_descr">
		<text>Alright, listen up. A group of stalkers tried to gang up on one of my boys not too long ago. Luckily he escaped, and is busy recovering in the medical hangar, but we can't let that kind of disrespect go.\n \nYou might need to round up your own posse before you take them on, but these guys tried to massacre my boy. Show them what happens to chucklefucks who try that.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="NE RABOTAETigi_task_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_kill_stalker_finish">
		<text>Done? ...Good.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- Dushman -->
	<string id="igi_task_cit_killers_merc_trader_stalker_task_kill_stalker_title">
		<text>Contract killer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_cit_killers_merc_trader_stalker_task_kill_stalker_descr">
		<text>I have been contracted to find and eliminate a target. I should return for payment once I am done.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_cit_killers_merc_trader_stalker_task_kill_stalker_job_descr">
		<text>Our contractor has a list of outstanding bounties. We need volunteers to carry out these hits discretely, which will allow us to fulfil our obligations to our contractor. Are you interested?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_cit_killers_merc_trader_stalker_task_kill_stalker_finish">
		<text>It is done? Great. Here's your percentage.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- Aslan -->
	<string id="igi_task_cit_killers_merc_barman_mlr_task_kill_stalker_title">
	<text>Eliminate the target</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_cit_killers_merc_barman_mlr_task_kill_stalker_descr">
		<text>Aslan will pay me to eliminate a target for him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_cit_killers_merc_barman_mlr_task_kill_stalker_job_descr">
		<text>Yes, we always have work. I'll give you the coordinates, you kill the target.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_cit_killers_merc_barman_mlr_task_kill_stalker_finish">
		<text>Well done, here's the cash.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- Sidorovich -->
	<string id="igi_task_drx_sl_esc_m_trader_task_kill_stalker_title">
	 	<text>Contract Killer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_drx_sl_esc_m_trader_task_kill_stalker_descr">
		<text>I've agreed to remove a thorn from Sidorovich's side. Once I'm done, I should return for my reward.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_drx_sl_esc_m_trader_task_kill_stalker_job_descr">
		<text>I have a list of outstanding bounties that need taking care of. These people tend to be unwanted plotters, frauds, slanderers... many of them have even roughed up my couriers or harassed my tourists in the past. In other words, they're all bad for business.\n \nPut one of these scumbags out of my misery, won't you? I'll be happy, the Zone will be a cleaner place, and you'll be well paid. Everyone wins!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_drx_sl_esc_m_trader_task_kill_stalker_finish">
		<text>You got rid of that filthy freak? Good riddance! Here is what I promised, and let it never be said that uncle Sidorovich doesn't reward good work.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- Rabbit -->
	
	<string id="igi_task_pri_monolith_monolith_trader_stalker_task_Assault_Stalker_title">
		<text>Conquer the Enemy</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_pri_monolith_monolith_trader_stalker_task_Assault_Stalker_descr">
		<text>You have been tasked to clear an area for the good of the almighty Monolith. Report back to Rabbit after the job is done.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_pri_monolith_monolith_trader_stalker_task_Assault_Stalker_job_descr">
		<text>I have an important mission for you. You must journey into the Zone and clear the area so that our forces may move in. Are you ready?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_pri_monolith_monolith_trader_stalker_task_Assault_Stalker_finish">
		<text>The task is done? Good. Praise Monolith.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="igi_task_pri_monolith_monolith_trader_stalker_task_kill_stalker_title">
		<text>Kill the Planner</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_pri_monolith_monolith_trader_stalker_task_kill_stalker_descr">
		<text>A stalker is trying to deactivate the Brain Scorcher. Kill him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_pri_monolith_monolith_trader_stalker_task_kill_stalker_job_descr">
		<text>There are many threats to the great works of the Zone. There is one who is once again planning to deactivate the Brain Scorcher. He must be stopped. You must find him and destroy him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_pri_monolith_monolith_trader_stalker_task_kill_stalker_finish">
		<text>You have done well. The Collective is pleased.</text>
	</string>
	
	
</string_table>